onlinenewspapers.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy OnlineNewspapers & OnlineMagazines Directories

**General**

Web Wombat (though its website www.onlinenewspapers.com) respects the privacy of all those who use the services we provide on that site. We have a simple policy that we will not wilfully disclose any personal information regarding our users without first obtaining their permission, unless required by law.

By using the web site www.onlinenewspapers.com, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy.

**Use of Cookies**

A "cookie" is a file sent to your browser by a web server and stored on your computer, it contains data that web sites use to identify you as a unique user.

Companies which advertise on our site may collect information from you if you click on their advertisements or access their sites. They may do this by using cookies. Due to the way the Internet operates, we cannot control this collection of information. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to your computer, giving you the choice whether to accept it or not.

If you have any questions or concerns about the way in which information is collected or used by another site, then you should contact whoever is responsible for that site directly.

**What Information does Web Wombat Collect?**

Web Wombat (though its website www.onlinenewspapers.com) does not collect any personal information about you (such as your name or email address) except when you specifically and knowingly provide that information. We do keep a record of the IP addresses from which users access our site. This data is used by us for internal administration, and to analyse the way in which people use our site, so that we can keep improving the services we offer. This data also provides us with anonymous and broad demographic information about those using our site.

**Does Web Wombat disclose information to anyone else?**

We may share information about the use of our site (www.onlinenewspapers.com) with advertisers, sponsors, content providers and other third parties. However, we only disclose aggregate, anonymous information about our users and will not disclose any personally identifiable information to any third party without your express consent.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like [**more information**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

For example, we may disclose the total number of "hits" the site receives, or how often the average user visits our site. Please be aware, however, that we will release any specific personal information we may hold about you if required by law.

**Email**

We receive and reply to email from users on a regular basis. For record-keeping purposes we retain copies of all incoming and outgoing email. Information in the email we receive or send will not be disclosed to any third party without the permission of the sender, either express or implied, unless required by law.

**Links**

The Onlinenewspapers site contains a large number of links to external sites. Please be aware that these external sites are developed by people over whom we have no control, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Onlinenewspapers site.

We encourage you to familiarise yourself with the privacy policy of any web site you visit which collects personal information, and to exercise discretion when providing such information.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our discretion and without notice. If we do, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will be made available on this site so that you remain aware of the data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Further information**

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions, comments or would like more information. Our email address is [newspapers@webwombat.com.au](http://www.onlinenewspapers.com/emailform/Feedback.htm).

This Privacy Statement is version 2.0, and replaces all previous versions.
